Anthony, from a investor perspective, do
you buy into the bearish macro takes
about oil prices, interest rates, the
geopolitics? What do you make of all
this?
>> I think those people are dumb.
>> Why?
>> Well, the stock market says they're dumb
because all that stuff keeps happening.
The stock market keeps going higher. So,
they're wrong. Like, the market is the
referee. And there was two different
opinions. One opinion was that interest
rates going higher would mean the stock
market would go lower. That's not right.
Why do I know that? Because the market
is the referee. Market went higher. Oil
prices are higher, stock market's not
supposed to go higher, right? Wrong.
Stock market went higher. So, you just
look at it like, forget what my opinion
is, forget what their opinion, like the
market is ultimately the one who's going
to tell you what the answer is. And if
you were an observer of the market, dare
I say a student of the market, the
market is going higher. So, regardless
of what your economics textbook said,
what your professor told you, what your
academic papers, what your theories,
none of that matters because the market
is going higher. And so, obviously,
something has changed. Now, some people
will say like, "Well, the market's
wrong." And they literally will be
arroant enough to believe that they're
going to somehow come and find, you
know, some mispricing in the market.
They're going to make a boatload of
money.
But most people are intelligent. They're
just going to say to themselves, well,
maybe something I thought about the
market is not true or something has
changed. I need to go and learn more
about this. I need to investigate this.
I need to approach it from the
perspective as a humble student who is
going to be taught. And the market is
the teacher. So if you do that, I think
that you'll end up finding that a lot of
things have changed in the market that
make it very different than 20 years
ago.
>> One of the things that I've been writing
about, you've been writing about is that
AI has essentially redefined the entire
macro picture. So that the Fed and all
the data that the academics watch aren't
as relevant as maybe a few years ago.
And I think that's playing out in real
time as we're sitting here. The S&P
500's right at record highs. We're
probably going to keep going higher
through midterms. All of that to me is
very bullish, but do you think that AI
is the only reason to ignore all the
macro data or are there other factors at
play here?
>> No, I think the AI story is a piece, but
it's actually a pretty small piece of
what's going on right now. Go back five
years. I mean, the beauty of being dumb
enough to put your opinions on the
internet is they're on the internet. You
can look at for years. I have been
telling everyone the economic data is
wrong. The Fed's wrong. The BLS is
wrong. These people can't count. It is
hilarious. They tell you that inflation
is X and you're like, "Cool. How'd you
count that?" And they explain it to you
and you literally want to bash your head
against the wall because you're like,
"These people literally don't know how
to count." And so that is true of the
jobs report. How many times do you have
to come out with a jobs report and then
a year later be like, "Oh, sorry. We
overcounted by a million." Like what? So
all of the economic data that people
have been looking at, it's just one big
scop. Bad data in leads to bad decision
out. And if the data is wrong, which I
have been saying for years and years and
years, then obviously you're going to
get people making the wrong conclusion.
So, fast forward to today. Now,
everyone's like, "Well, I don't
understand. Do I think the oil price is
wrong?" No, the oil price is made by a
market. That is a correct reading.
Great. Do I think the interest rate is
wrong? 100%. I think that the Fed could
not tell you what the actual inflation
rate is. So if they don't know what the
inflation rate is then they have to sit
and they have to go come up with here is
the interest rate of which we want to
set the price of money. How many people
experience that actual interest rate?
Not everybody. The interest rate then
what do people do? They come out and
they say well here's what the interest
rate is set at and I'm going to be over
or under that. So in reality it's a
different rate that you're actually
paying. Then everyone experiences it
differently. And so one of the things
that I've been talking about now for
years, personal inflation rate. If the
government comes out and says inflation
is 3.5%, great. That doesn't mean 3.5%
for me. I live in New York City.
Everything's expensive. Way more
expensive than if I lived in, you know,
somewhere in Iowa. No disrespect to the
people in Iowa, but like I'm jealous of
them. They got way lower cost of living.
And so is their inflation higher or
lower? Well, it depends on what is the
mix of goods and services that they
consume. And so that person that's
sitting in Iowa has a very different
inflation rate than me sitting in the
middle of Manhattan. But then you go and
you look at in Iowa, the guy who lives
in downtown Iowa, you know, no-name town
has a different inflation rate than the
farmer who's dealing with fertilizer
prices and gas prices and all this stuff
spiking on him. And so it just comes
back to this [clears throat] idea of
what people are ultimately trying to do
is they are trying to make these very
kind of broadstroke analysis of an
economy. And frankly, the people who are
the most confident that they're smart
end up being the most wrong. So the
Bears, they're like perpetually just
wrong. But even more importantly is go
look at the academics. How many of the
academics have been correct over the
last, I don't know, 5 years or so.
Almost none of them. I don't think that
there's a single academic that's
navigated this correctly. By the way, h
why is that not a big deal? Because the
people who are paid millions of dollars
a year to navigate haven't even been
that good at it. So you look at this
like this is a very complex dynamic
environment where everything is
changing, the data is changing. So the
question then becomes, what should you
do? Well, many of the best investors in
the world, they opt out. They don't play
the game. They're not trying to figure
out what's going to happen to the stock
market in the next 3 weeks. They simply
say, "I want to buy great companies that
I can hold for a long period of time."
Or they buy hard assets and they say,
"The government's never going to stop
printing money. I'm just going to hold
these assets because I know they're
going to be inflated because of the
government printing." Like the best
investors realize the game everyone else
is playing is a bad game. It's
unwinable. I'm going to go play a game
where I either have an edge or I believe
something about the world that other
people aren't disciplined enough to
believe. Why is Warren Buffett rich?
Because he's disciplined. Why are
bitcoiners and gold holders and land
holders rich? Because they're
disciplined. They don't go chase the
latest sexiest thing. And so if you
bring this back to the AI story, what
percentage of people in America use AI?
It's not a 0%, but it's not like we have
80% of people using AI yet. What
percentage of people pay for AI? I
believe the latest number is 2%. Why is
that number crazy? Cuz 5% of Americans
say that they spend money on sports
gambling. So more people in America
right now, two and a half times more
people spend money on sports gambling
than on AI. And you're telling me AI is
the say all beall about the economy? I
think it's a big part. I think it has a
big impact, but I would argue that
there's more GDP coming from consumers
like the consumer contribution to GDP on
sports betting. More dollars are going
there when you look at the actual credit
card data. So, it comes back to I am as
bullish on AI as anybody. But I think
that AI all of a sudden became a safe
way to talk about this taboo thing which
is no, the economic data has been wrong
and will continue to be wrong because
the people who are counting don't know
how to count and the systems that they
have put in place are antiquated. So AI
comes along and everyone's like, "Oh,
this system, it didn't have AI in it."
Like, "No, you guys just didn't know how
to count inflation for the last two
decades." And that's why we got $40
trillion in debt. We got a trillion
dollar annual expense. And on top of all
of that, they just keep printing money
because they're just looking at bad
data. And so, hey, let them do what
they're going to do. I'm not here to
complain about it. I'm not going to
change their mind. Just buy the assets
that they're going to make go up in
price and chill. This episode is
sponsored by Yall Street Asset
Management. If you own a gold or silver
ETF, the vast majority of its metals are
likely stored in foreign vaults under
foreign jurisdictions. That's why Yall
Street built YSAU, the Yall Street
physical gold ETF, and YSA, the Yall
Street Physical Silver ETF. The physical
gold and silver backing these funds are
not only fully allocated bars, but 100%
of the metal is held in the United
States at Texas Precious Metals
Depository. You get the simplicity of an
ETF while knowing the physical gold and
silver itself is held here in America in
fully allocated bars. The accessibility
of Wall Street with the independence,
[music] common sense, and
entrepreneurial spirit of Texas behind
it. If where and how your gold and
silver allocation is vaulted matters to
you, check out YSAU and YSA. To learn
more about the funds, visit
yallreefs.com.
So, one of the things that against that
entire backdrop you're describing, you
have also been writing about how
Bitcoin, gold, and land are essentially
the three evergreen assets for a complex
macro backdrop that you're describing
here. lay out why you like these assets,
but I I think it's somewhat intuitive,
but I want to hear from you.
>> Well, I think most people uh they
believe that productive assets drive
returns. That is demonstrabably false.
The stock market, almost all of the
gains in the stock market are driven by
money printing. How do I know that? The
S&P over the last five years is up about
70%. Bitcoin, gold, and land is up 170%.
When you denominate the stock market in
gold at various points, including over
the last 25 years,
gold is either flat to outperforming the
stock market depending on what days you
pick. So when you think about that for
like, wait a minute, how is it that
these productive assets that are
supposed to be so much better than these
non-productive assets, why is it that
they have the same or worse performance?
It's because it's all money printing.
So, your real rate of return is not what
you're being sold. And until people
realize that, then they're going to go
chase all this stuff. Now, guess what?
I've made a lot of money investing in
private companies, even in public
companies. I'm not saying you can't make
money. I'm saying on an overall basis,
if you're just buying the S&P index,
this great return you think you're
getting, you see, oh, I got 12% last
year. You didn't get 12%.
So, you got something way worse than
that. and you go and you look at various
assets and you say to yourself, what do
I want to hold for the next 10 years?
Do you think let's let's play a game. Do
you think Microsoft's going to be around
in 10 years?
>> Totally.
>> Okay. You think they're going to be
around in 20 years?
>> Yes.
>> Maybe. I don't know. I I literally have
no clue. I think that they're doing a
pretty good job. Seems like it's a good
business. Seems like it's growing. Seems
like they've done a great job
positioning themselves for the AI, you
know, industry, etc. Right, dude. Do you
see what is coming out of the labs? Do
you see how fast this stuff is coming?
What if all of a sudden we just don't
need to use Microsoft Excel anymore
because the agents just do all the work
for us? Is that going to happen tomorrow
or not? I have no clue. So, if you just
go back like remember chatbt came out
three years ago. Fast forward to now,
it's a whole different world. We have
new models coming out, new intelligence.
Take for example the recent uh data MKER
uh or Merkor came out with a study. It
had frontier models take an accounting
test do a bunch of accounting uh
examples. It beat 12 different mid-level
to senior accountants at doing it. But
not just the accountants scored if I
remember the data correctly the
accountant scored a 37% on the tasks and
it took them like five times as long.
the frontier model scored 100%.
And it took them like less than 10
minutes on each task. So you look at
that and you say to yourself, are
accountants going to go away? Absolutely
not. But accountants aren't going to be
doing these individual tasks that
frankly were just this like rope
memorization or was very kind of minute
detail. And people are like, what are
you talking about? There's no way. Okay,
let's go back in time. A 100 years ago,
there used to be buildings with multiple
floors full of bookkeepers who were
writing with [ __ ] feathers and ink
numbers and closing the books at the end
of each month or quarter. And they were
keeping track of revenue and expenses
and net income and all these things, but
they would do it in physical paper. And
it took armies of people to do this for
these big companies.
All of those people, their jobs got
automated away. They got freed up to go
do more productive things and it got
boiled down into a piece of software
called Excel or called Stripe.
There's nobody who's like, "Woe is the
accountants. We really screwed over the
accountants." I don't know the exact
data. My guess is that there's probably
more accountants or more people working
in the finance uh departments than there
was back then because we were able to
empower all of these businesses to now
allocate their resources, keep track of
revenue and expenses and net profit etc.
And then that led to an explosion of
more companies which meant that there
was more people that we needed to employ
not less. So you go back to is Microsoft
going to be around? I think so. But I
don't know
100% positive that the land, the dirt's
going to be around, gold's going to be
around, Bitcoin's going to be around.
These hard assets that are built on
resilience and we're entering a world
where there's incredible uncertainty and
there's this dynamic changing
environment. So Microsoft, I think
people have kind of a very specific
connotation about. Let me go to a
different business, Netflix. You think
Netflix is going to be around 20 years?
>> They're looking shaky today. So I I
don't know.
>> We don't know. There's people who think
Netflix will be a zero 5 years from now.
I'm not saying they're right. Right. But
like that's a company that I think
people are like, "Okay, that's a little
bit more in the gray area over 20
years." So you just go through the stock
market and you say, "How many of these
companies are we for sure positive are
going to be here in 20 years?" And how
many of them could be disrupted? Because
with Netflix, well, what happens if all
of a sudden AI content creation comes
along? Well, Netflix could embrace it.
They could say, "Hey, we're going to put
this up, right?" But what if all of a
sudden content becomes personalized and
now it's choose your own adventure in
the content. If now I'm watching the
movie and the t television recognizes
I'm watching with my child and so it
plays certain scenes because the kid is
there versus if I watched it without the
kid I'd get different scenes. Could
Netflix embrace that? Is that different?
How does that work? All of these things
become very different, right? And so
then you start thinking, well, what
about the viewing experience? Well, what
if all of a sudden now I watch Netflix
when I'm in my car because my car drives
itself? How does that experience change?
What if the screen size? You start to
play this game, right? So, the reason I
say all this is we don't know where the
future is going. What I try to do is I
try to barbell it. I want to own things
that I have a high degree of confidence,
are very resilient, and can withstand
all the change, all the uncertainty. And
then I basically want to invest in
things that are trying to ride the wave
of disruption, use new technology and
create something from scratch that ends
up being very valuable in the future. So
most of my portfolio is Bitcoin or
similar types of assets and private
investments in early stage startups. And
I think putting those two things
together, one is full of uncertainty,
one to me is very certain. One is
illquid, small, highly volatile. The
other one has decreasing volatility,
very liquid, and I think now that it's
become very understood, is only going to
be permeating more and more into
portfolios. You put those two things
together, it's kind of like portfolio
theory, right? If you put a bunch of
risky assets that are non-correlated or
or volatile assets that are
non-correlated together, shouldn't that
increase the sharp ratio, decrease the
risk, and lead to a higher return?
That's how I think about investing
personally as well.
One quick note everyone, YouTube is
telling us that 80% of you are not
subscribed to the channel. If you want
to help this channel grow and help me
continue to book great guests, the
single best thing you can do is hit that
subscribe button. I really appreciate
it. Now, let's get back to the episode.
So, the the boring assets, Bitcoin,
gold, and land, those are the forever
items to hold. And then you can almost
sprinkle in the moonshots is is the way
to think.
>> You say it better than me. I should just
let you answer that question.
>> So, okay. One one question I have for
you. You've obviously been investing in
Bitcoin for a very long time. How do you
see the
>> Not long enough, Phil. Not long enough.
>> Well, no, no one's early enough in
Bitcoin. Um, if we think about the
proliferation of AI, you said something
like 2% of people use AI right now. How
does that change or impact the thesis on
Bitcoin? Or maybe there's no impact. I
don't know.
>> Well, I think that there's a couple of
aspects that are happening. one um if
you look at the short term there was a
capital rotation from people who were
excited about Bitcoin and
cryptocurrencies into AI and capital
chases returns right and so if all of a
sudden there's all this value being
created every single day Bitcoin or
crypto investors woke up and they were
tempted they said this thing's not going
anywhere it's going sideways to down all
my friends are getting rich buying XYZ
company
screw it I'm going to sell some of this
and go over here and so you got this
rotation the best place to see where
this happened was in Korea I remember
talking to somebody from Korea They were
like, "Dude, crypto
that's old news. We gambling on the AI
stocks now, right?" And so they like
Korea is actually very interesting
because it is a dichotomy or or kind of
like a magnified example of what's
actually happening globally. They're
just a little bit more public about it.
So capital rotation in the short term. I
tweeted back, I think it was in May or
June. I said, "It is going to be
glorious when the AI profits rotate back
into Bitcoin. You should go read the
comments." People respond at times like
you're an idiot. Bitcoin's over. AI is
great, blah blah blah, all this stuff,
whatever. Well, guess what happened
recently? Bitcoin all of a sudden went
from down significantly on the year to
now it's basically back to flat. Why
why' that happen? It jumped from $65 to
$85,000.
AI trades started to cool off a little
bit. All the easy money, as my friend
Jordi Visser would say, started uh kind
of disappear. It became a little bit
harder. Now I got to figure out where
are these memory names actually
sustainable? How much upsides left? How
do I allocate across power, energy, u
you know, data centers, memory, chip,
like all these things?
or hey this Bitcoin thing's out of
favor. What if I I frontr run that?
Isn't that going to come back at some
point? So you get some capital rotation
stuff you got to pay attention to.
Second thing that's happening is with
the rise of AI agents now all of a
sudden you're actually increasing the
addressable market for a lot of
technologies. So I would argue that
payment companies who are able to
embrace aic payments they're going to do
very well because now you just literally
have more transactions more quoteunquote
users even though they're digital users
versus human. Well same thing is
happening with Bitcoin and crypto. So,
Bitcoin, stable coins, many of these
products, AI agents need digital money.
And so, now you're expanding the total
addressable market. In Bitcoin's case in
particular, you are not increasing the
supply. And so, Bitcoin is one of the
only assets in the world where when
demand increases, supply stays constant.
And so, guess what has to happen? Price
has to go up in order to accommodate
everybody. And so, I think that it will
start very slowly, but it'll be one of
these things, you know, slowly then
suddenly. and you you're seeing it like
I don't know we have a public company
inside that public company there are
more agents that work at that company
than humans I don't think we're unique I
think that's most companies and so right
now for the most part I don't think a
lot of the agents are doing like
financial transactions they're not
necessarily buying stuff that's not like
hey we give it you know some sort of
credit card or something but like that's
going to change and so if that is kind
of the path here then the intersection
of AI and crypto or AI and Bitcoin is
you have an acceleration. Like we're in
AI time now. Okay. Well, you need assets
that can keep up. Today at 4:00, what's
going to happen? Market's going to shut
today at 2 o'clock. What's going to
happen? The bank is going to put down
their little window and say, "No more
wires till tomorrow." 2:00.
The agents, they working. Let's go.
Let's move the money. Right? They don't
got time for two o'clock. They don't
even know what two o'clock is. So that's
the change that's going to happen is
you're going to get a move in technology
because the actual demand from the
market is going to force it.
>> If it's that clear to you what's the
case to keep buying gold then?
>> Well, I think that gold is ultimately
just a hedge on uh government printing.
And frankly, I don't have tons of gold,
right? It's not like I'm like some huge
gold bug, but I just think that Bitcoin,
gold, and land, and land in particular,
like productive land. Um, I think is uh
a great way to uh kind of blend the
volatility. Bitcoin is much more
volatile than gold or land. And so there
are years where it's amazing and then
there are years where it might drop 40
50%. And so that used to be 85%, so it's
only 40 or 50%, you know, kind of like a
draw down for ants. But you still want
to be able to have some things in there
that kind of blend that over time. you
want to have, you know, some degree of
non-correlation. Um, and so I think that
that bucket together is pretty
interesting for folks.
>> I agree. I I think the Bitcoin story is
getting more and more interesting as
technology moves faster. And you you've
said this before, Bitcoin is gold with
wings. It's only going to fly further
and faster than gold.
>> The gold bugs don't like that. But yes,
that is true.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Um, okay, Anthony, I got to
ask you, you just came out with this new
book, How to Live an Extraordinary Life,
Volume Two. And the cover is sweet,
right?
>> The cover is sweet. I like it a lot. Um,
what are your biggest lessons or
takeaways in this? Cuz I believe there
are 49 or 50 chapters.
>> I say there's 50 chapters. 49 lessons.
>> 49 lessons. What stands out to you as a
favorite?
>> You've written a book a book before,
right? The first book I wrote, I I sat
down, wrote it all up, sent it to the
publisher. I said, "I'm a genius." I
went back, read it six months later. I
said, "This is pretty good." I give
myself maybe like a B B+ if I'm being
really kind to myself. But writing a
book is you got to learn how to write a
book, right?
>> It's not easy.
>> So, I said, you know, I I need another
crack at that. I got a whole Apple note
uh notes on my phone. Every time I've
heard a great idea for the last almost
decade, I just put it in my Apple notes.
And these are ideas I could hear it on a
podcast, see it in an interview, talk to
a friend, learn it, you know, real hand
uh firsthand experience, whatever. Put
it in there. And so I said, you know, I
I need to I need to write a write an
even better version of this. first one
did very well, bestseller, translated a
bunch of different languages around the
world. I was pretty shocked actually um
that it did well. Um and uh so I said,
"What if I wrote the 50 best ideas? Go
through this really, you know, kind of
sit and do it." So I spent a year kind
of honing the craft of writing the book.
And uh this one's a A for sure. I don't
know if I'll ever hit a A+, but this
one's a A compared to the first one.
This one's even better. And um some of
the chapters I think are uh pretty
unique that you're not going to read
another book. Like uh the most
controversial maybe we'll start there.
Don't get outworked by a crackhead.
>> People hear that and they're like wait
what?
>> Crackhead wakes up every single day.
He's got no resources, got no food, got
no plan, but got to survive. And what
does a crackhead do? It figures it out,
right? And so crackheads, we shouldn't
make, you know, light of the situation.
There's obviously a national epidemic uh
that people are dealing with in terms of
drug addiction and all this stuff, but I
think that it's an extreme example to
show that there are people all around
the world who have way less resources
than you. They have way less
connections. They have way less of a
plan, yet they figure out every single
day how to accomplish their goals. And
so, don't get outworked by a crackhead.
Is this mantra of someone somewhere with
way less than you've got is going to
figure it out today. You better figure
it out, too. So tell me uh I see a
chapter here called the ego tax. What is
that?
>> Ego tax is how much do you care about
being right versus being actually known
for it. Right? How much of it is hey I'm
doing something because uh it's going to
stroke my ego versus I'm doing the right
thing. And ultimately what you find is
if you do things in pursuit of basically
stroking your ego that's the tax because
usually it ends up doing things that you
wouldn't otherwise do. And so think of
it as like the modern example be like
doing it for the gram, you know, doing
it for Instagram. Great. But you end up
with this like vapid life that you're
probably not that happy. You probably
actually didn't accomplish the things
that you wanted to. And even worse is
you get captured by the audience. So it
pulls you in this weird direction, but
like it was all an ego tax. It was a tax
to pull you away from the thing that you
actually wanted. And so if you can get
rid of the ego tax and just focus on
what is it that I actually want, be
intentional, have agency, and go after
it. But I think that your life ends up
much better.
>> What about procrastination is an
arrogant assumption.
>> Procrastination is the idea that I'm
going to have time later to do this.
It's pretty arrogant, right? Who said
God's going to give you more time? So
why don't you just go get it done now?
And so when you think about it from that
perspective, it's like, hey, I'll do it
next week. Well, who says you're going
to be here next week? and you start to
think about, oh, I literally assumed
that I will have more time, but if this
is important, let me get it done right
now because that's not promised to me.
So, you start thinking through that, but
then you take it a step further. It's
like, okay, like what is success?
Success is being excited to go to work
every day and being excited to come home
every day. What percentage of Americans
can measure their life through that lens
and say, "I'm successful." There's a lot
of people who say, "Man, I am so excited
to come home every day, but I hate my
job. I dread going to work every day.
Then there's a whole another contingent
of people who say, "Dude, I love my job.
I work with awesome people working on
exactly what I want to be working on. I
ain't trying to go home. I got arguments
with my spouse. My kids are acting
crazy. That ain't for me." There's a
very small percentage of people, I
think, that could say genuinely, I'm
excited to go to work every day. I'm
excited to come home every day. Do those
two things. What is What is success
other than that?
>> That's the best way to define it. Uh, I
love that. Last one here and then I'll
let you go. Anthony, amateurs built
Noah's Ark. Professionals built the
Titanic.
>> That's a [ __ ] banger. [laughter]
>> It is. Good. Tell me what it means.
>> When people look at problems, usually
the first thing they do is, "Let's go
get an expert. Let's go get someone
who's done this before." But what you
end up finding is that actually
expertise can be a liability sometimes.
So the example I use is if you want to
go to the doctor, you want an expert. I
don't want to go get surgery from an
amateur, right? I want to get somebody
who's done it a million times, knows
what they're doing, they're an expert,
they're going to do uh a surgery. Same
thing if I go to court, I want somebody
who knows what they're doing. They know
the law, they've been here, they
practice, they got a license, all this
kind of stuff. But those are defined
problems that have been solved before.
So in cases where the problem is
something that we know has been solved
before, then you want an expert. But
sometimes, many times, when you're
trying to solve something that's never
been done before, you don't want
experts. You want amateurs who can look
at a problem from a new way. You want
amateurs who can look at something and
say, "I know all the experts think this
isn't possible. Reusable rockets never
been done before." You needed somebody
who was never in the rocket business to
come in and say, "No, I think it's
possible. Here's how we should do it.
Let's go try." And so, it's not that
expertise is good or bad. It's just that
you got to understand what is the
problem I'm trying to solve. If it's a
solvable problem from the past, we need
an expert. If it's something that has
never been solved before, maybe we
should consider getting people who
haven't done this before, but who bring
specific advantages to this problem. So,
you go back to amateurs built Noah's
Arc, but the professionals built the
Titanic.
Noah's Arc ain't sink. Titanic sitting
at the bottom of the ocean.
Wow. Um, Anthony, I super appreciate
your time. Everyone should definitely go
buy this book. I have a few copies at
home. Send some to my parents as well.
Uh, shout out Phil's parents.
>> Great work on this. And uh, we'll do
this again soon. Thank you very much.